ktradionetwork.com 2013-05-08

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy explains how this site treats “personal information.”  “Personal Information” is information that is personally identifiable like a name, address, e-mail address, social security number or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. 

This site is owned and operated by KT Radio Network Inc. for your personal use and information.  By accessing and browsing this site, you are accepting, and are bound by, this Privacy Policy.

_**Categories of Personal Information Collected**_

We receive and collect the following categories of personal information.

  * Information that you provide: for example, we may collect information received from Kevin’s Insider E-mail Club, e-mails, communications and comments submitted through this site and other correspondence you send.
  * Information collected by our Web servers:  when you visit this site, our Web servers may automatically collect your “internet protocol” (IP) address and information about the web page that you visited immediately prior to visiting our site. 
  * Cookies:  a cookie is a small text file that is sent to your Web browser from a Web server and stored on your computer’s hard drive.  When you visit this site, a cookie may be sent to your computer.  You can control whether or not you want to accept cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser. 

**_Use of Personal Information Collected_**

  * We may use the information that visitors provide us to respond to correspondence, improve our site, inform visitors of new products and services, and for informational or other developmental purposes.
  * We may use the information collected by our Web servers to help us track our visitors use of the site, analyze traffic patterns, record session information, store visitor’s preferences, and identify sources of web traffic to our site. ** **
  * We may use cookies to record session information, such as items that visitors add to their online shopping cart.
  * We **** reserve the right to share your personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your email, postal address, and phone number with affiliates and third parties. In the event that our company or its assets are acquired by or merged with a third party, the information collected by our site may be one of the assets transferred.
  * We may also use personal information to investigate, prevent or take action against suspected illegal activities, problems with this site, or as required by law. We may use the information for legal proceedings, such as responding to subpoenas, court orders, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.
  * The use of comments, stories, articles, pictures and videos submitted by visitors to KT Radio is governed by a Release and Terms & Conditions, which are available on this site.

**_Sites Not Covered By This Policy_** ** __**

This Policy does not apply to websites that this site links to, websites that link to this site, websites framed by this site, or any other third party websites.  KT Radio is not responsible for the content, products or services on those sites. 

When you purchase any products offered from this site, you will be automatically directed to the manufacturer’s website. In addition, when you download any broadcast of The Kevin Trudeau Show, you will be automatically directed to iTunes.  These sites are third-party websites that are not controlled or operated by KT Radio. You should visit those third-party websites to determine the privacy policy and terms of use that govern those sites.

**_Security Measures_**  
Our web hosting company uses industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer information exchanged with our site.  Our web hosting company has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site.  Although we believe that our web hosting company provides appropriate security measures, we are not responsible for the practices, actions or inactions of that company.

**_Changes To This Policy_**  
We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and without advanced warning, by updating this page. You are bound by any such revisions and should therefore review this Privacy Policy every time you visit this site. __

**_Terms & Conditions/Release_**  
Nothing herein waives, limits or in any way modifies our Terms & Conditions or Release.

**_“Opt Out Rights”_**  
If, at any time after visiting the site, you change your mind about receiving information from the site or sharing your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy, you may request an opt out, by contacting us.

**_No Children Under 18_** __  
This site is not directed to, nor does it knowingly collect any personal information from children under 18.   If a child who we know to be under age 18 sends personal information to us online, we will only use that information to respond directly to that child, notify parents or seek parental consent.

**_Questions or Additional Information_**  
If you have any questions about this Policy, or if you would like additional information, please do not hesitate to contact us at  28 E. Jackson, Building #10-A940, Chicago, IL 60604. 

Last Updated: July 16, 2009
